

Web Developer

2 Cantera Circle Greenville, SC 29615 864-449-7072 frazierr2@gmail.com ThinkFrazier.com github/frazierr2

Objective

As a graduate of an accelerated front end web development program, I am seeking a position that will allow me to use and grow my new skills as a developer, utilize my past experience as a system administrator and a tech support analyst to be a well-versed and unique asset to any team.

RELEVANT SKILLS

LANGUAGE AND PRACTICES

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

JSX

Git and GitHub

JSON

AJAX

RESTful Api's

FRAMEWORKS AND LIBRARIES

Backbone JS

React JS

Underscore JS

Bootstrap

Sass

Handlebars

jQuery

PROJECT

U-GRUB

https://frazierr2.github.io/final-project/

The goal for U-Grub is to allow you, the user, to record your restaurant experience and later recall the things you liked, didn't like, food you ate and more. If you're traveling, no worries, we have you covered there also. Simply go to the Search Local Eateries tab and type in your location and you will be given a list of local restaurants with all the information you will need to make an informed decision.

EDUCATION

Front-End Engineering

The Iron Yard, September 2016 - December 2016

Bachelors of Science in Business Administration and Sociology

Winthrop University, August 2004 - May 2009

WORK EXPERIENCE

SYSTEM INTEGRATOR AND TECH SUPPORT ANALYST

Lucas Systems Inc.

May 2014 - August 2016

Integrate hardware and software to facilitate clear communication between all devices across the IT system. Run network cables through walls and ceilings and terminate ends into patch panels and junction boxes.

Install PC's, Point-of-Sale terminals, switches, routers and monitors in restaurants.

Provide technical assistance and support in person, phone and electronically related to computer systems, hardware and software.

IT COORDINATOR, WEBMASTER, YOUTH MINISTER

Mount Tabor United Methodist Church May 2009 - May 2014

Designed and managed two websites through two campuses using WordPress, HTML5 and CSS3.

Troubleshoot, diagnose and repair equipment and networks across multiple campuses.

Managed Social Media aspects of the church and ministries. Recruit, equip and supervise a group of dedicated adult volunteers to lead the Middle School youth ministry of the churches two campuses.